const questions = [{
    question: 'Bob and Linda are the cutest couple. When is their wedding anniversary?',    
    answers: [
      'February 14',
      'June 1',
      'September 3',
      'November 17'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'September 3'
  },
  {
    question: 'Gene was pressured into going out with Courtney, the most annoying girl at school. But her dad is just too cool! What does Gene like about Courtney\'s dad?',    
    answers: [
      'Extensive keyboard collection',
      'Epic beatboxing skills',
      'Pro-wrestling career',
      'His mascot collection'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Extensive keyboard collection'
  },
  {
    question: 'When Bob and Linda opened up a B\&B their first guest was Javed.  What was his occupation?',    
    answers: [
      'Optometrist',
      'Entomologist',
      'Meteorologist',
      'Zoologist'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Entomologist'
  },
  {
    question: 'While the kids were at Morts.  Bob and Linda were on vacation for alone time. After getting into his lazy pants, what was the first thing Bob did?',    
    answers: [
      'Setup his Battleship for One game.',
      'Illustrate the comic book he was working on.',
      'Build a model of the bus from Speed',
      'Ordered a burger.'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Build a model of the bus from Speed'
  },
  {
    question: 'Millie is Louise\'s #1 fan. For halloween she wanted to be what costume duo with Louise?',    
    answers: [
      'Dust Bunnies',
      'Pinky and The Brain',
      'Batman and Robin',
      'Cat and Dog'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Dust Bunnies'
  },
  {
    question: 'Delivering sandwiches is just a job.  What instrument does Jonas play?',    
    answers: [
      'Keyboard',
      'Airboard',
      'Drums',
      'Melodica'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Melodica'
  },
  {
    question: 'Theres a ghost in the basement! Linda, Tina, Gene, and Louise use the oujia board to communicate with the ghost. What is the ghost\'s name and age?',    
    answers: [
      'Tyler, 12',
      'Jeff, 13',
      'Joshua, 14',
      'Alex, 16'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Jeff, 13'
  },
  {
    question: 'When Bob was 14 he tried to make Henry a new specialty burger. What was it?',    
    answers: [
      'Crispy Brinkley Burger',
      'Greed is Gouda Burger',
      'Baby you can Chive my Car Burger',
      'Bob\'s specialty Burger'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Baby you can Chive my Car Burger'
  },
  {
    question: 'Tina went with Darryl to the Valentine\'s day dance so she could make Jimmy Jr. jealous. Who was Darryl trying to win over?',    
    answers: [
      'Tabitha Johansson',
      'Louise Belcher',
      'Rosa Batista',
      'Samantha Jones'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Rosa Batista'
  },
  {
    question: 'Linda loves Bob so much, she left her fiance for him.  Who was she engaged to?',    
    answers: [
      'Teddy',
      'Hugo',
      'Mort',
      'Phillip'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Hugo'
  },
]